lyricstime.com 2008-12-17

# Privacy - Lyrics Time

### Privacy Statement

Lyrics Time has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our company's firm commitment to the privacy of our visitors. Lyrics Time respects the privacy rights of consumers, and strives to offer a factual site built on trust and consumer confidence. Information Collection Lyrics Time is the sole owner of the information collected on www.lyricstime.com; Lyrics Time collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site. 

### Registration

When you try to access certain area in Lyrics Time Registration is required. During registration a user is required to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact the user about services on our site for which he has expressed interest. It is optional for the user to provide demographic information (such as income level and gender), and unique identifiers (such as, username and password). 

### Information Use

During the process of delivering an ad to you, Lyrics Time does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address. However, Lyrics Time does obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example). The information collected by Lyrics Time is used for the purpose of targeting ads and measuring ad effectiveness on behalf of our advertisers. 

### Profile

We store information that we collect through cookies, log files. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users those details their viewing preferences. Consequently, collected information is tied to the users’ personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user. This profile is used to tailor a user’s visit to our Web site and to direct pertinent marketing promotions to them. We do no share your profile with other third parties. 

### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user’s hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. here By setting a cookie on our site, users would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If users reject the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. Persistent cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. See the “Profile” section. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. 

### Third Party Advertising

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by [THIRD PARTY AD SERVER NAME], our Web advertising partner. Information about users’ visit to this site, such as number of times they have viewed an ad (but not user name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to users on this site. For more information about [THIRD PARTY AD SERVER NAME], cookies, and how to "opt-out", please click here This privacy statement covers the use of cookies www.lyricstime.com. only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

### Log Files

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We use log files to analyze user movement Communications from the Site 

### Special Offers and Updates

We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections. 

### Newsletter

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections. 

### Customer Service

We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the user’s wishes. 

### Sharing

Legal Disclaimer Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. 

### Choice/Opt-out

Our users are given the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for information. For example, our order form has an ‘opt-out’ mechanism so users who buy a product from us, but don’t want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists. Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email by contact us. 

### Links

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we,. Lyrics Time, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

### Surveys & Contests

Our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Anonymous Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. Users’ personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties unless we give prior notice and choice. Though we may use an intermediary to conduct these surveys or contests, they may not use users’ personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

### Tell-A-Friend

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend’s name and email address. Lyrics Time will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. Lyrics Time does not store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. 

### Chat Rooms, Message Boards, and Public Forums

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example on message boards, through e-mail, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, by posting personal information online that is publicly accessible, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. 

### Security

This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line. If users have any questions about the security at our Web site, users can send an email by contact us. 

### Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information

If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users’ personally identifiable information. This can usually be done or by emailing our Customer Support by contact us. 

### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If, however, we are going to use users’ personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days 

### Contact Information

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.
